Emeka Okwor

A creative software engineer and a javascript enthusiast offering 3+ years of experience building software applications with Javascript. Skilled in developing and building multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a software engineer.

Lagos State, Nigeria, NG.

+2348163955616

Email: emartinsokwor@gmail.com GitHub: https://github.com/chubbyst

rings

Portfolio: https://emekaokwor.tech LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/emekaokwor

EXPERIENCE

SeamlessHR, Lagos — Frontend Engineer

Tech Stack: Vue,

JUNE 2022 - Present

• Part of the frontend team building and maintaining the SeamlessHR Application

Decagon, Lagos — Software Engineer

Link: https://decagonhq.com/fellowship/

Link: https://decagon.institute/

Tech Stack: Javascript, React, Vuejs, Node Js.

NOVEMBER 2020 - JUNE 2022

- A member of the frontend team managing development projects from initial design through completion, optimizing all cross-browser and multi-platform compatibility.
- A member of the frontend team developing and maintaining the Decagon Enterprise app.
- Conversant with Agile methodologies.

 ${f Krystal\ Lab\ Solutions}, {f Lagos-Junior\ Full stack\ Developer}$

Tech Stack: Angular, React, Vue, Node Js.

JULY 2019 - MARCH 2020

- Designed, built, and maintained clients' websites
- Worked closely with the development team to proffer solutions and decide on technologies to use.
- Gained more exposure to developing real-life applications.

Simba Travels and Logistics, Lagos — Junior Web Developer

Tech Stack: PHP, Javascript, VUE, Angular

MAY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019

- Built and maintained company website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, and PHP.
- Part of a team that built the staff portal with PHP and VUE.

TECHNOLOGIES

- React Js
- Vue Js
- Angular
- Node Js
- Express Framework
- Typescript
- Javascript
- JQuery
- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- SASS
- Vuetify
- Material UI
- Tailwind
- GraphQL
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQLMYSQL
- Firebase
- Version Control with Git and GitHub.
- Docker
- CI (Travis CI)
- Test-Driven Development.
- Cypress
- Jest
- Mocha

LEARNING & BOOTCAMPS

Andela DevC core track, Lagos — Fullstack Developer

Project Link: https://teamplay-app-e48a7.firebaseapp.com/

MAY 2019 - JULY 2019 Tech Stack: Node JS, VUE

Moat Academy Lagos - Fullstack Development

JANUARY 2018 - MARCH 2018 Tech Stack: PHP, Javascript

PERSONAL PROJECTS

MUSIC BOX:

A music streaming web App,

Technologies Used - React.Js, Node Js, Typescript, SASS, MongoDB.

Link: https://themusicbox.netlify.app/

PUNTER-MASTERS:

A social app for bettors or punters.

Technologies Used – Vue, Vuetify, Node JS, Express, Firebase, Paystack,

and flutterwave integration

Link: https://punter-masters.web.app

SCRUM POKER GAME:

An interactive scrum poker pointer game.

Technologies: Vue 3, Node JS, Express, socket.io, Typescript, MongoDB.

Link: https://scrumpokagame.herokuapp.com/

JOB FINDER:

A Job portal where users can search and apply for jobs, using categories like

Technology, Manufacturing, etc. Employers can also post jobs.

Technologies Used - React.Js, Node Js, Typescript, MongoDB.

Link: https://job-finder-2.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

Federal University Of Tech, Owerri, Nigeria

Bachelor of Science in Food Science, May 2011

CERTIFICATIONS

Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC) - SCRUMstudy - Accreditation Body for Scrum and Agile

Vue Js 2 the complete guide - Udemy

Learn About Agile Project Management and SCRUM - OpenClassrooms